(Sheldon:)That's when Amy said,
"Want to make this interesting?"
"Make this interesting"?
(Penny:)You bet money on me?
(Sheldon:)No, no.
(Sheldon:)We designed an experiment
involving you.
(Sheldon:)See? Now, isn't that
interesting?
(Penny:)It's not interesting.
(Penny:)It's incredibly insulting.
Okay, (stammers)
maybe this will help--
(Sheldon:)imagine you're holding a pen.
(Sheldon:)Before you go too far,
not a special pen
(Sheldon:)with your initials
engraved on it--
(Sheldon:)that'll make the next part
really hard.
(Sheldon:)Oh...
(Penny:)That's it.
Get out!
(Sheldon:)I don't understand
why you're mad at me.
(Sheldon:)You should be mad
at Amy.
(Sheldon:)Like I was
this afternoon.
(Sheldon:)Hey, look at that--
I let it go.
Get out!
SHELDON:
Penny?
What?
(Sheldon:)I think I left
my pen in there.
(Bernadette:)I understand
why you're upset,
(Bernadette:)but he worked really hard
to get the store ready.
(Bernadette:)And it's just furniture.